http://bbklaw.com/privacy

Commitment to our Clients
We offer our clients a commitment that is long lasting and unique.
Employee Benefits & Executive Compensation
Private Representation: Employee Benefits & Executive Compensation
California Coastal Act
California Environmental Quality Act (CEQA)
Land Use, Planning & Zoning
National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA)
Land Use, Planning & Zoning
Local Agency Formation Commission (LAFCO)
Government Policy & Public Integrity
Local Agency Formation Commission (LAFCO)
Sexual Harassment Avoidance Training for Supervisors
The Brown Act “Open Meetings Law”
Privacy & CCPA Policy
Best Best & Krieger LLP values the privacy of its website users. We do not take lightly the responsibility of protecting your personal information. Through this policy, we intend to be transparent about how your information may be collected, used and secured.
California residents have additional rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act, also known as CCPA. To learn more about these rights, please click here.
Types of Information Collected and How They’re Used
Through our website, BB&K collects information in two ways: (1) automatically and (2) directly from a website user.
Information Collected Automatically
When you access our website, BB&K collects information about your connected devices (such as a computer, mobile phone and tablet) and how you navigate through our webpages. This type of information includes:
IP address, domain information, browser type and geographic location (as associated with your IP address). Collecting this information allows us to become more familiar with who visits our website, how often they visit and what webpages they visit.
Cookies. Cookies are small files the website places on your hard drive for identification purposes, such as a unique user ID. BB&K uses cookies to keep records of the pages you visit and your activity on our website. This information helps us to evaluate and provide better information and services to our clients and website users. Cookies are also used to improve our website navigation structure. To view our cookie policy, please click here. Please review your browser’s instructions for information on accepting, deleting and managing cookies. If you choose to not accept cookies, you may limit access on our website and the functionality of our webpages.
Information Submitted Directly by a Website User
BB&K provides you the opportunity to agree or decline to give your personal information. We will inform you of the purpose for the collection and do not intend to transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described in the “How We Share Information” section below. If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we may transfer that information within our organization or to a third-party service provider as necessary.
BB&K website users will generally submit personal information through:
Website forms (such as our Contact Us, Subscribe and event registration forms). This information is used to either provide a service or communicate with our website users. The information submitted by you may include, but is not limited to:
First and last name
Company, home, postal or other physical address
Telephone number
Email address
Company name
Job title, position or occupation
Industry
Personal interests
Any other information needed to provide a service you requested
By using these forms you also agree to our Terms of Use.
Direct Email. BB&K has direct email links to its legal professionals and staff on its website. Although this information is not sent through the website, it can be retained and used to help process your request. Be advised, sending emails over the Internet may not be secure and should not contain sensitive or confidential information unless the messages are adequately encrypted. No attorney-client relationship is created through your use of this website or sending an email to a BB&K attorney. Unsolicited information sent to BB&K by individuals who are not clients of the firm is not subject to any duty of confidentiality. BB&K and you must agree that there is an attorney-client relationship. Until such a relationship exists, BB&K will assume that any information you send to us does not meet the standard of attorney-client privilege.
How We Share Information
All data on this website, with the exception of event/webinar payments made through our payment processing provider, ClientPay, are housed in a third-party-hosted SQL database with cloud storage. Access to this database is limited to BB&K and its third-party website development team. We do not have access to the financial information used in ClientPay.
We do not sell the information you submit through forms on our website and only share this information, with your consent, with third-party providers for website analytics or when required to complete a service you have requested.
We will disclose your personal information, if required to do so by law, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our website.
How Your Information is Secured and Stored
All data on this website are accessed through certificate verified Transport Layer Security, also known as TLS, and stored encrypted-at-rest. We do not store sensitive personal information, such as financial information, or legal documents on this website.
Children’s Privacy
Children under 16 years old are not the target audience for our website. To protect their privacy, we prohibit the solicitation of personal information from these children. If we receive or discover personal information provided by a child under the age of 16, we will promptly delete the information.
Links to Other Websites
Our website may contain links to third-party websites. We do not share your personal information with those websites and we are not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of all websites you visit.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change, modify or update this policy at any time without notice, with terms of the old policy subject to the terms of the new or updated policy. Any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information will be posted on this page prior to implementation.
This policy was last updated on June 1, 2020.
If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@bbklaw.com.
California Privacy Policy for California Residents
This privacy policy for California residents supplements the information contained in the Best Best & Krieger LLP general Privacy Policy. This California Privacy Policy only applies to those individuals or households who reside in California. We adopt this policy to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, known as CCPA, and any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this Policy.
Your Rights Under the CCPA
The CCPA grants the following rights to all California residents:
Right to Know: you have the right to know what personal information BB&K has collected, used, disclosed or sold in the last 12 months, both as to the categories and specific pieces of personal information.
Right to Delete: you have the right to request deletion of personal information held by BB&K and, by extension, a service provider used by BB&K.
Right to Opt-Out: California residents have the right to opt-out of the sale of personal information. BB&K does not sell your personal information (as ‘sell’ is defined in CCPA) and therefore does not provide an opt-out option.
Right to Non-Discrimination: you have the right to non-discrimination in terms of price or service when a consumer exercises a privacy right under CCPA.
Exercising Your Rights Under CCPA
To exercise your right to know and right to delete information, California residents must submit a verifiable request.
You can submit a request in two ways:
By calling toll-free: (844) 999-0649
By submitting an Online form
As a resident of California, you may make a personal information request twice in a 12-month period. BB&K will respond within 10 days to confirm receipt of the request and provide information on how the request will be verified and processed. BB&K will provide a response to the request within 45 days of the verifiable consumer request.
BB&K will not disclose, in response to a Request to Know, your Social Security number, driver’s license number or other government-issued identification number, financial account number, any health insurance or medical identification number, an account password, security questions and answers, or unique biometric data generated from measurements or technical analysis of human characteristics. BB&K shall, however, inform you with sufficient particularity if we have collected this type of information.
Verifying Your Request
For BB&K to respond to your Request to Know or Request to Delete, we must first verify your identity. BB&K may use a third party verification service, or will request you submit verifiable information. The information you will be asked to provide depends on the type of request you make and the sensitivity of the information.
Generally, a Request to Know the categories of personal information held by BB&K will require you to provide two types of verifiable consumer information. The same may apply to a Request to Delete. A Request to Know or Delete sensitive personal information may require you to provide at least three types of verifiable consumer information.
If BB&K is unable to verify the identity of the requesting consumer, information will not be given and you will be notified of this reason for denial in BB&K’s response.
Authorized Agent
If you are submitting a Request to Know or Request to Delete through an authorized agent, BB&K will require you to provide the authorized agent written and signed permission to do so, verify their own identity directly with BB&K, and directly confirm with BB&K that they provided the authorized agent permission to submit the request. These requirements will not apply should you provide the authorized agent with a power of attorney.
Categories of Information Collected
BB&K may collect personal information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household.
The following table lists the categories of personal information, as defined by the CCPA, that has been collected within the past 12 months, and how this information has been used and shared.
Personal Information Categories & Examples
Source Categories
Purpose(s) for which the Information was Collected
Categories of Third-Party Sharing
Personal Identifiers such as name, address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, Social Security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.
Website information is collected from the website user or their connected device while they are interacting with our website.
Contact information is collected directly from an individual, website user, client or other contact.
Website information is used to improve our web-based offerings and website functionality. Tracking movement within our website allows us to better understand user preferences and enhance our user interface.
Contact information is used to provide services to our clients or website users, perform contracts, marketing communications, protect against fraud or illegal activity, and business operations.
All data collected from our website is stored in a third-party-hosted database with cloud storage. This database is only accessed by BB&K and its third-party website development team.
Website information is shared with our website analytics service providers.
Contact information is shared with third parties when it’s necessary to provide a service and at the consent of the consumer. This information may also be shared with our business operation and business software providers.
Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)), such as bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, health insurance information, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, or employment history.
This information is collected through client and employee background and verification checks, electronic communications, intake paperwork completed during the course of business, regular accounting procedures conducted during the course of business, and the pursuance of employment opportunities.
This information is used to provide services to our clients, perform contracts, marketing communications, protect against fraud or illegal activity, to employ staff members, and business operations.
Financial information is shared with our business operation providers to complete a sale or purchase of a service at the consent of the consumer.
Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law, such as age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, or veteran or military status.
This information may be collected through client and employee background and verification checks, electronic communications, intake paperwork completed during the course of business, and the pursuance of employment opportunities.
This information may be used to provide services to our clients, perform contracts, protect against fraud or illegal activity, and to process employee intake forms required by the state and federal government.
Information given on employee forms will be shared with the state and federal government, as required by law.
Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
This information is collected via electronic communications, submission of forms on this website, intake paperwork completed during the course of business, and regular accounting procedures conducted during the course of business.
This information is used to provide services to our clients, enhance web-based offerings, perform contracts, marketing communications, protect against fraud or illegal activity, and in business operations.
This information is shared with third parties when it’s necessary to provide a service and at the consent of the consumer. This information is also shared with our business operation and business software providers.
Biometric information, such as fingerprint technology.
This information is not regularly collected during the course of business; however, it may be used in the duration of employment for authentication (fingerprint/facial recognition technology).
This information may be used in business operations for employees to securely access computers, tablets or phones.
We do not share this information.
Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, browsing history, search history and information regarding a consumer's interaction with an Internet website, application or advertisement.
Employee interaction with an external website.
This information is collected directly or automatically from consumers through their interaction with our website.
Employee information is collected when an employee browses external websites while logged into our internal network.
This information is used to improve our web-based offerings and website functionality. Tracking movement within our website allows us to better understand user preferences and enhance our user interface.
Employee data is collected for security purposes.
Consumer information is shared with our website analytics service providers.
Employee information may be shared with our business operation and business software providers.
Geolocation data.
This information is collected directly or automatically from consumers through their interaction with our website.
This information is used to improve our web-based offerings and website functionality.
This information is shared with our website analytics service providers.
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory or similar information.
This information may be collected during the course of business through electronic communications or recording devices.
This information is used to provide legal services to our clients and educational program participants.
Video and audio may be shared as a part of normal business operations.
Professional or employment-related information.
Defined above in rows one, two, three and five.
Use of information explained above in rows one, two, three and five.
We may share this information as explained above in rows one, two, three and five.
Education information, defined as information that is not publicly available personally identifiable information as defined in the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Sec. 1232g; 34 C.F.R. Part 99).
This information is collected through client and employee background and verification checks, electronic communications, submission of forms on this website, intake paperwork completed during the course of business, regular accounting procedures conducted during the course of business, and the pursuance of employment opportunities.
This information is used to provide services to our clients, perform contracts, marketing communications, protect against fraud or illegal activity, to employ staff members, and business operations.
This information is shared with third parties when it’s necessary to provide a service and at the consent of the consumer. This information is also shared with our business operation and business software providers.
Inferences drawn from other personal information to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities or aptitudes.
This information is collected directly or automatically from consumers through their interaction with our website.
This information is used to improve our web-based offerings and user interface.
This information may be shared with our website development team and website analytics service providers.
Cookie Consent
By clicking “Agree,” you agree to the storing of cookies on your device to enhance website navigation, analyze website usage and assist in our marketing efforts. View our Cookie Notice here.
Agree
Decline
